[
    {
        "question": "1. Why is it good to learn about the water cycle?",
        "answer": "SoÂ we can protect the water and future generations will have water."
    },
    {
        "question": "2. What do we call SOLID water?",
        "answer": "Ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. How many stages is the water cycle?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Where does the water go in EVAPORATION?",
        "answer": "Into the air."
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Where does the water come from in TRANSPIRATION?",
        "answer": "From plant leaves."
    },
    {
        "question": "6. What is PRECIPITATION?",
        "answer": "Water that falls back down to the ground."
    },
    {
        "question": "7. CONDENSATION happens when the water in the clouds gets ____ and turns back into aliquid.",
        "answer": "cold"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Water is so important because...",
        "answer": "It helps to keep the temperature on Earth stable. (Not too hot, not too cold)"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. How can we help?",
        "answer": "Take 3 showers a day."
    },
    {
        "question": "10. How much water on Earth is fresh water?",
        "answer": "3%"
    }
]